DOR TAYARI

FULL STACK WEB DEVELOPER

PERSONAL INFO



(+972) 53-827-8886



dortayari@gmail.com



Hatena 380, Achiezer, Israel



linkedin.com/in/dor-tayari



https://github.com/DorTeri

SKILLS

| Programming languages:

- TypeScript
- JavaScript
- Python
- C++

| Frontend:

- HTML5
- CSS
- SASS
- TailwindCss

| Backend:

- Node.js
- Express.js
- MongoDB
- RestAPI
- GraphQL

| Frameworks:

- React, Redux
- Vue, Vuex
- Angular, RXJS
- Next.js

LANGUAGES

- English | Advanced
- * Hebrew | Native

OBJECTIVE

Graduated from Coding Academy, intensive bootcamp of 640 hours. As a Full Stack Web Developer, I bring a wealth of experience in developing and implementing complex web applications. I am proficient in a variety of frameworks and a passion for problem-solving. Always wants to learn more and increase my knowledge in this area. I'm also a friendly person.

EDUCATION

FULL STACK WEB DEVELOPER

Jan 2023 - May 2023

Coding Academy Bootcamp | Ramat - Gan, Israel

Completed the course with distinction and best final project of all the courses before. Asked to work with Coding Academy after the course.

INVESTMENT PORTFOLIO

Sep 2021 - Mar 2022

Psagot College | Rehovot, Israel

Completed the course with distinction, asked to teach a new subject area to the next courses.

FULL MATRICULATION

Sep 2016 - Sep 2018

Mekif-Yehud | Yehud, Israel

PROJECTS

PORTFOLIO - https://dors-portfolio.onrender.com

SNAPGRAM - A social media app inspired by Instagram.

SOMEDAY - An end-to-end team management app inspired by Monday.

ONESTYLE-ISRAEL – A shoes store built with React.

APPSUS - An all-in-one app inspired by Gmail.

WORK EXPERIENCE

SPORTS HALL COORDINATOR

Sep 2022 - Now

Municipality | Hemed, Isarel

Organized and hosted sport events and was responsible for handling the cleaning company.

CLEANING SERVICES MANAGER

Jul 2021 - Aug 2022

Municipality | Hemed, Isarel

Managing cleaning workers in several places in the center district.